Herb Staehr Collection ARC.0029
Library and Archives
- Series VI: Concert, Studio, and Television Recordings [RESTRICTED], circa 1960s-2000s
  - Subseries 2: DVD-Video, circa 1960s-2000s
    - Allman Brothers
      - Macon, Georgia, 1991 December 31 (Box 7, Object 79-80)
      - Ohne Filter Extra, 1991 (Box 7, Object 81)
      - Beacon Theater, New York, New York, 1992 March 17, 1992 March 22 (Box 7, Object 82-83)
      - U.S. tour, 1992 June 22 (Box 7, Object 84)
      - Beacon Theater, New York, New York, 1994 April 1 (Box 7, Object 85)
      - Woodstock '94; Rock Hall Induction; House of Blues; Late Show With David Letterman, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Object 86)
      - Austin City Limits; Farm Aid, 1996, 1997 October 4 (Box 7, Object 87)
    - Allman, Greg
      - Daytona Beach, Florida; Des Moines, Iowa, 1987 (Box 7, Object 88)
      - Molson Park Blues Festival, Barrie, Ontario; The Cannery, Nashville, Tennessee, 1988 August 27, 1988 November 11 (Box 7, Object 89)
      - The Cannery, Nashville, Tennessee, 1988 November 11 (Box 7, Object 90)
      - Inside Track with Graham Nash; John Lee Hooker Blues Show, Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 1990 (Box 7, Object 91)
    - Animals
      - Eugene, Oregon; Wembley, London, BBC-TV special, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Object 92)
      - Eric Burdon and the Animals: Finally...; VH-1 Behind the Music, 1991 (Box 7, Object 93)
    - B-52's: Westfallenhalle, Dortmund, Germany, 1983 May 15 (Box 7, Object 94)
    - Bad Company
      - Various including BBC Top of the Pops, Don Kirshner's Rock Concert, Midnight Special, 1974-1979, undated (Box 7, Object 95)
      - Orlando, Florida, 1999 May 21 (Box 7, Object 96)
    - Badfinger: various including Concert For Bangladesh; Beat Club; Director's Cut, 1971, 1997, undated (Box 7, Object 97)
    - Baez, Joan: various including Newport Folk Festival, Smothers Brothers Show; Woodstock, Bill Graham Memorial, 1969-1991, undated (Box 7, Object 98)
    - Baker, Ginger
      - Various including Gonks Go Beat, Beat Club, unreleased interview, 1970, 1980-1989 and undated (Box 7, Object 99)
      - In Africa, 1971 (Box 7, Object 100-101)
      - Baker-Gurvitz Army, "Musikladen" concert, 1975 (Box 7, Object 102)
      - Baker, Ginger and Band, Vienna, Austria -- concert and interview, 1982 March 15 (Box 7, Object 103)
      - The Late Show, 1988 June 10 (Box 7, Object 101)
      - Rehearsals at S.I.R. Studios, Los Angeles, California, 1988 October 26 (Box 7, Object 104-105)
      - Ginger and Fri ends, 1988 October-1988 December (Box 7, Object 106-107)
      - With Tim Bogert and Keith Wyatt, Musician's Institute, Hollywood, California, 1988 December 5 (Box 7, Object 108)
      - Primal Scream sessions, Acton, California, January 1989 (Box 7, Object 109)
      - With J. Hellborg and D.D. Perkins, Malibu, California, 1989 February 1 (Box 7, Object 110)
      - "50th Birthday Super Jam" with Randy California, Tim Bogert, Robby Krieger, Los Angeles, California; Fairfax High, Hollywood with Leslie West, Edgar Winter, Hollywood, California, 1989 (Box 7, Object 111)
      - Grogg and Tankard, Baltimore, Maryland, 1990 June 24 (Box 7, Object 112)
      - With Jonas Hellborg and Johann Johanson, Vienna, Austria, 1992 January 29 (Box 7, Object 113)
      - With Jonas Hellborg, Weiden, Germany, 1992 February 12 (Box 7, Object 114)
      - With Jonas Hellborg, Austria, 1992 (Box 7, Object 115)
      - With Bill Frisell and Charlie Haden, Frankfurt Jazz Festival, Germany, 1995 August 26 (Box 7, Object 116)
    - Baldry, Long John: various including Shindig! Goes to London with Brian Auger and Trinity; Maintenance Shop, Ames, Iowa, 1967, 1985, undated (Box 7, Object 117)
    - The Band
      - Band is Back, Queen Elizabeth Theater, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1984 (Box 7, Object 118)
      - Woodstock '94, Saugerties, New York; Today Show, 1994 August 13-1994 August 14 (Box 7, Object 119)
      - Lost Waltz, 2006 (Box 7, Object 120-121)
    - Bangles
      - Live in concert (MTV); Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1986 (Box 7, Object 122)
      - Greatest Hits videos; Suzanna Hoffs In Concert; VH-1 Behind the Music, 1990-1991, 2000 (Box 7, Object 123)
    - BBM (Baker-Bruce-Moore): various including "Where in the World" promo; ABC In Concert; Sonoria Festival, Italy, 1994 (Box 7, Object 124)
    - Beach Boys
      - Various including Jack Benny Show, Ready, Steady, Go!, An American Band, 1985 and undated (Box 7, Object 125)
      - Various including "Fun, Fun, Fun" and "Please Let Me Wonder", Ready, Steady, Go!, An American Band, 1985 and undated (Box 7, Object 126)
    - Beatles
      - Ed Sullivan Show live performances and videos; Tokyo, Japan, 1964-1968 (Box 7, Object 127)
      - Paris, France, 1965 (Box 7, Object 128)
      - 25 Jahre Beatles; Nobody Told Me; Anniversary Stories, 1984-1985, 1994, undated (Box 7, Object 129)
      - Private Reel promo compilation; It Was Twenty Years Ago Today, 1985, 1987 (Box 7, Object 130)
    - Beck, Jeff
      - St. Louis, Missouri; Omni, Atlanta, Georgia, 1989 October 29, 1989 November 19 (Box 7, Object 131)
      - Centrum, Worcester, Massachusetts with Stevie Ray Vaughan on encore, 1989 November 8 (Box 7, Object 132)
    - Bee Gees
      - 1975-1979, 1989 and undated (Box 7, Object 133)
      - 1988 and undated (Box 7, Object 134)
      - 1990 March 17 and undated (Box 7, Object 135)
      - Bee Gees: The Live History; Virgin Music biography, 1993 December and undated (Box 7, Object 136)
    - Benatar, Pat
      - Various including American Bandstand, Don Kirshner's Rock Show, Friday's, 1979-1980, undated (Box 7, Object 137)
      - U.S. Festival; BBC In Concert, 1982, 1985 (Box 7, Object 138)
      - Veterans Memorial Coliseum, New Haven, Connecticut; Tour Rehearsals, 1983, 1986 (Box 7, Object 139)
      - Montreal, Canada, 1986 February 21 (Box 7, Object 140)
      - Various including Women in Rock, Tonight Show Starring Johnny Carson, 1992, undated (Box 7, Object 141)
    - Berry, Chuck: Paris, France, 1972 (Box 7, Object 142)
    - Betts, Dickie
      - Grugahalle, Essen, Germany, 1978 March 4 (Box 7, Object 143)
      - Guitar Greats concert, Capitol Theater, Passaic, New Jersey; Bayou Club, Washington, D.C., 1984, 1988 October 30 (Box 7, Object 144)
    - Bishop, Elvin: various including Welcome to the Fillmore East; MTV Rock Influences: The Blues, 1970-1971, 1991, undated (Box 7, Object 145)
    - Blind Faith: Hyde Park, 1969 June 7 (Box 7, Object 146)
    - Blue Oyster Cult: Capitol Center, Largo, Maryland, 1976 December (Box 7, Object 147)
    - Bonoff, Karla: University of Hiroshima Peace Concert, 1986 August 6 (Box 7, Object 148)
    - Bruce, Jack
      - Various including Swing In and Out Front, 1971 and undated (Box 7, Object 149)
      - Jack Bruce Band, Old Grey Whistle Test with Mick Taylor and Carla Bley, 1975 (Box 7, Object 150)
      - Various including Charlie Watt's Big Band, North Sea Jazz Festival, Old Grey Whistle Test, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Object 151)
      - Rutgers University, New Jersey, 1980 March 25 (Box 7, Object 152)
      - Grugahalle, Essen, Germany, 1980 October 18 (Box 7, Object 153)
      - Various including Rockpalast, Germany and Golden Palominos, Montreux, 1983, 1986 (Box 7, Object 154)
      - With Kenji Suzuki and Anton Fier; Hamburg, Germany with Sting, 1987 November, 1988 May 1 (Box 7, Object 155)
      - Sunday Night with Joe Walsh; Spectrum, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1988 (Box 7, Object 156)
      - Bottom Line, New York, New York, 1988 October 10 (Box 8, Object 1)
      - Bayou Club, Washington, D.C., 1988 October 12 (Box 8, Object 2)
      - Rock Life with Rory Gallagher, Cologne, Germany; Jimi Hendrix Tribute Concert, Germany, 1990, 1991 (Box 8, Object 3)
      - Various including Gala Concert and Guitar Legends, Seville, Spain with Phil Manzenera and Joe Cocker, 1990, 1991 (Box 8, Object 4)
      - Budapest, Hungary, 1991 July 6 (Box 8, Object 8)
      - Warsaw, Poland with Blues Saraceno and Simon Philips, 1992 (Box 8, Object 5)
      - Absolutely Live, Clopham, England; Frankfurt Jazz Fest, 1992, 1993 (Box 8, Object 6)
      - 50th birthday concert with "Ginger" Baker
        - Germany with Ginger Baker and Gary Moore, 1993 (Box 8, Object 7-8)
        - Rockpalast with interviews, 1993 (Box 8, Object 9)
      - Various European TV shows; People in Room #8, undated (Box 8, Object 10)
    - Bruce, Jack and Ginger Baker
      - Bayou Club, Washington, D.C., 1989 November 29 (Box 8, Object 11)
      - MTV News; Bottom Line, New York, New York, 1989 December (Box 8, Object 12)
      - Headline News; N.A.M.M. Show, Anaheim, California, 1990 January 7, 1990 January 19 (Box 8, Object 13)
      - The Strand, Redondo Beach, California, 1990 January 23 (Box 8, Object 14)
      - Flood Zone, Richmond, Virginia, 1990 February 2 (Box 8, Object 15-16)
      - Bayou Club, Washington, D.C., 1990 February 4 (Box 8, Object 16-17)
      - Late Night with David Letterman; Toad's Place, New Haven, Connecticut, 1990 February 9, 1990 February 11 (Box 8, Object 18)
      - Toad's Place, New Haven, Connecticut, 1990 February 11 (Box 8, Object 19)
      - Hammerjacks, Baltimore, Maryland, 1990 February (Box 8, Object 20)
    - Buchanan, Roy
      - Introducing Roy Buchanan, 1971 (Box 8, Object 21)
      - Austin City Limits; Rockpalast, Hamburg, Germany, 1977, 1985 February 24 (Box 8, Object 22)
      - Markethalle, Hamburg, Germany, 1985 February 24 (Box 8, Object 23)
      - Horseshoe Tavern, Toronto, Ontario, 1987 December 1 (Box 8, Object 24)
      - Various including Music Express News and Custom Made, 1987-1988 and undated (Box 8, Object 25)
    - Buckingham, Lindsey: PBS Center Stage, Chicago, Illinois, undated (Box 8, Object 26)
    - Burdon, Eric
      - Eric Burdon Band, Loreley, Germany, 1982 August 28 (Box 8, Object 27)
      - Comeback, 1983 (Box 8, Object 28)
    - Cale, J. J.: Bottom Line, New York, New York, 1990 March 16 (Box 8, Object 29)
    - Canned Heat
      - Various including Monterey Pop Festival, Beat Club, Montreux Jazz Festival, Old Grey Whistle Test, 1967-1974 (Box 8, Object 30-31)
      - Various including Germany and Ripley's, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania with John Mayall, 1982 November 1, 1983 (Box 8, Object 32)
      - Canned Heat: Boogie Assault, 1983 (Box 8, Object 33)
      - Boogie with Canned Heat, undated (Box 8, Object 34-35)
    - Cars: Houston, Texas; Live Aid, JFK Stadium, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1984, 1985 July 13 (Box 8, Object 35)
    - Cash, Johnny
      - Johnny Cash on Campus, 1970, 1974 December 30 (Box 8, Object 36)
      - Johnny Cash Show compilation, undated (Box 8, Object 37)
    - Clapton, Eric
      - Various with Yardbirds, John Mayall's Blues Breakers, Cream, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Object 38-39)
      - Various with Dirty Mac, Blind Faith, Plastic Ono Band, 1968-1969 and undated (Box 8, Object 40)
      - Rock and Roll Years, BBC-4; Cream: Royal Albert Hall [rebroadcast, BBC-4], 2005 April 29 (Box 8, Object 41)
      - Various with Delaney & Bonnie and Friends and Derek and the Dominoes, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Object 42)
      - Various including Concert for Bangladesh, The Who's Tommy, Alex Korner's Birthday Jam, 1971-1979 (Box 8, Object 43-48)
      - Interview with Mary Travers, 1975 July 11 (Box 8, Object 49)
      - 8mm films, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Object 50)
      - Eric Clapton and His Rolling Hotel, 1978 (Box 8, Object 51-52)
      - Various including Secret Policeman's Other Ball, Bill Graham Tribute, Roger Waters' Pros and Cons of Hitch Hiking Tour, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Object 53)
      - Action into Research for Multiple Sclerosis (A.R.M.S.) concerts with interviews, 1983 (Box 8, Object 54-56)
      - Hodern Pavilion, Sydney, Australia, 1984 November 20 (Box 8, Object 57)
      - Tour rehearsals, Brixton Academy, London, England, 1985 February (Box 8, Object 58)
      - Behind the Sun MTV profile; Live Now!, 1985 April 17, 1985 May 1 (Box 8, Object 59)
      - Montreal Forum, Quebec, Canada, 1985 May 3 (Box 8, Object 60-62)
      - Theatro Tenda, Milan, Italy, 1985 October 27 (Box 8, Object 63)
      - Various including "Forever Man" promo, Late Night with David Letterman, Live Aid, 1985 (Box 8, Object 64)
      - Brixton Academy, 1985 (Box 8, Object 65)
      - Montreux Jazz Festival, Switzerland, 1986 July 9-1986 July 10 (Box 8, Object 66-75)
      - Juan Les Pins Festival, Antibes, France, 1986 July 12 (Box 8, Object 76-78)
      - Various including Prince's Trust Rock Concert, "Tearing Us Apart" promo, Fox Theater with Chuck Berry, 1986 (Box 8, Object 79)
      - Various including "It's in the Way That You Use It" promo, Top of the Pops, Ebony Showcase Theater with B. B. King, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Object 80)
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 1987 January 12 (Box 8, Object 81)
      - Pala Europa, Rome, Italy, 1987 January 29 (Box 8, Object 82)
      - Sports Complex, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1987 April 21 (Box 8, Object 83)
      - MTV interview [complete with time slate], 1987 April 30 (Box 8, Object 84)
      - Budokan Hall, Tokyo, Japan, 1987 November (Box 8, Object 85)
      - The Man and His Music, 1987 (Box 8, Object 86)
      - Various including Island Records 25th Anniversary, South Bank Session with Buddy Guy, Prince's Trust Rock Concert, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Object 87)
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 1988 February 4 (Box 8, Object 88-89)
      - Hammersmith Odeon, London, England [Dire Straits with Eric Clapton], 1988 June 8 (Box 8, Object 89)
      - Freedomfest -- Free Nelson Mandela Concert, Wembley Arena, London with Dire Straits, 1988 June 11 (Box 8, Object 90)
      - Civic Arena, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1988 September 4 (Box 8, Object 91)
      - Spectrum, Philadelphia,, Pennsylvania, 1988 September 7 (Box 8, Object 92)
      - Capitol Center, Largo, Maryland, 1988 September 8 (Box 8, Object 93-94)
      - Civic Center, Hartford, Connecticut, 1988 September 10 (Box 8, Object 95)
      - Nassau Coliseum, Uniondale, New York, 1988 September 11 (Box 8, Object 96)
      - Shoreline Amphitheater, Mountainview, California, 1988 September 21 (Box 8, Object 97-99)
      - Maple Leaf Garden, Toronto, Canada, 1988 October 7 (Box 8, Object 100)
      - 11:00 PM [Japanese television] clips and interview; Tokyo Dome, Tokyo, Japan with Elton John -- 25th Anniversary Tour, 1988 October 31, 1988 November 2 (Box 8, Object 101)
      - Tokyo Dome, Tokyo, Japan; Japanese interview, October 31, 1988, 1988 November 1 (Box 8, Object 102)
      - Budokan Theater, Tokyo, Japan with Sting and Elton John, 1988 November 4 (Box 8, Object 103)
      - Dunsfold Village Hall, Surrey, England with Gary Brooker and Friends, 1988 December 23 (Box 8, Object 104-105, 107)
      - Various including Much Music interview, International Rock Music Awards, Michelob commercial, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Object 106)
      - Chiddingford, England -- "No Stiletto Shoes" Band, 1989 December 23 (Box 8, Object 107)
      - Various including Jimi Hendrix South Bank documentary, "Pretending" and "Bad Love" promos, Night Music with David Sanborn, 1989 (Box 8, Object 108)
      - Various including The Journal interview, Convention Center, Atlantic City, New Jersey with The Rolling Stones, Entertainment This Week, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Object 109)
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 1990 January 22-1990 February 9 (Box 8, Object 110-120)
      - Palatrussardi, Milan, Italy, 1990 February 26-1990 February 27 (Box 8, Object 121-122)
      - Frankfurt, Germany, 1990 March 5 (Box 8, Object 123-124)
      - Saturday Night Live dress rehearsals and promos with Debra Winger, 1990 March 24 (Box 8, Object 125)
      - Omni, Atlanta, Georgia, 1990 March 28 (Box 8, Object 124, 126)
      - Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 1990 April 2 (Box 8, Object 127-129)
      - Meadowlands, East Rutherford, New Jersey, 1990 April 3 (Box 8, Object 130)
      - Spectrum, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1990 April 4 (Box 8, Object 131-134)
      - Nassau Coliseum, Uniondale, New York, 1990 April 6 (Box 8, Object 134-137)
      - Centrum, Worcester, Massachusetts, 1990 April 10 (Box 8, Object 138)
      - Civic Center, Hartford, Connecticut, 1990 April 12 (Box 8, Object 139-140)
      - Hilton Coliseum, Ames, Iowa, 1990 April 20 (Box 8, Object 140-141)
      - Meadowlands, East Rutherford, New Jersey, 1990 August 5 (Box 8, Object 142)
      - Spectrum, Philadelphia, 1990 August 14-1990 August 15 (Box 8, Object 143-145)
      - Nassau Coliseum, Uniondale, New York, 1990 August 17 (Box 8, Object 146-149)
      - Cincinnati, Ohio; St. Louis, Missouri, 1990 August 23, 1990 August 31 (Box 8, Object 150)
      - Sandstone Amphitheater, Kansas City, Missouri, 1990 August 28 (Box 8, Object 151)
      - Estadio Nacional, Santiago, Chile, 1990 September 29 (Box 8, Object 152)
      - Estadio Centemario, Montevideo, Uruguay, 1990 October 3 (Box 8, Object 153)
      - Estadio Riverplate, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1990 October 5 (Box 8, Object 154-155)
      - Saturday Night Live; International Rock Awards; Knebworth Festival, 1990 (Box 9, Object 1)
      - Various including American Music Awards, ABC In Concert, Sunday Comics, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Object 2)
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 1991 February 28, 1991 March 4 (Box 9, Object 3-14)
      - MTV Unplugged [complete with alternate takes], 1992 January 16 (Box 9, Object 15)
      - Spectrum, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1992 May 4 (Box 9, Object 16-20)
      - Civic Center, Hartford, Connecticut, 1992 May 6 (Box 9, Object 20-22)
      - Meadowlands, East Rutherford, New Jersey, 1992 May 8 (Box 9, Object 23-24)
      - Omni, Atlanta, Georgia, 1992 May 23 (Box 9, Object 25)
      - Stadio Comunal, Bologna, Italy, 1992 July 6 (Box 9, Object 26-27)
      - "White Room" at Montreux Jazz Festival, Switzerland, 1992 July 12 (Box 9, Object 28-29)
      - Civic Arena, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1992 August 11 (Box 9, Object 30)
      - Shea Stadium, New York, New York, 1992 August 21 (Box 9, Object 31)
      - Various including Week in Rock, "It's Probably Me" and "Runaway Train" promos, 1992 (Box 9, Object 32)
      - Various including MTV Music Awards, Bob Dylan's 30th Anniversary Concert, child safety public service announcement, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Object 33)
      - Various including Apollo Theater Hall of Fame, ABC In Concert, Saturday Night Live, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Object 34)
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, 1994 February 21, 1994 February 28 (Box 9, Object 35-38)
      - From the Cradle -- Conversation with Clapton, 1994 August 3 (Box 8, Object 39)
      - VH-1 From the Cradle Manhattan Center Studio rehearsals, 1994 September 28 (Box 9, Object 39-41)
      - Maple Leaf Garden, Toronto, 1994 October 5-1994 October 6 (Box 9, Object 42-44)
      - Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 1994 October 8-1994 October 10 (Box 9, Object 45-48)
      - U.S. Air Arena, Landover, Maryland, 1994 October 12 (Box 9, Object 49)
      - Through the Ages; ABC In Concert, 1994 November 6, 1994 November 18 (Box 9, Object 50)
      - Fillmore, San Francisco, California, 1994 November 7-1994 November 9 (Box 9, Object 51-53)
      - VH-1 Rarities, 1994 November 18 (Box 9, Object 54)
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 1995 February 23 (Box 9, Object 55)
      - Forum Assago, Milan, Italy, 1995 May 1 (Box 9, Object 56)
      - Arena, Miami, Florida, 1995 September 5 (Box 9, Object 57)
      - Spectrum, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1995 September 13 (Box 9, Object 58)
      - Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 1995 September 17-1995 September 18 (Box 9, Object 59-61)
      - United Center, Chicago, Illinois, 1995 September 24 (Box 9, Object 62-64)
      - Various including "Q" Merit Award, The Leo Fender Story, Danny Boy, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Object 65)
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 1996 February 18, 1996 February 23 (Box 9, Object 66-68)
      - VH-1 Duets with Dr. John; Prince's Trust Rock Concert, 1996 May 9, 1996 June 29 (Box 9, Object 69)
      - Various including Armani private party; MTV Unplugged with Baby Face, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Object 70-71)
      - Legends -- Montreux Jazz Festival, Vienna, The Hague, Vitoria, Spain, 1997 July (Box 9, Object 72-79)
      - Nippon-Budokan, Tokyo, Japan, 1997 October 27 (Box 9, Object 80)
      - VH-1 Legends, 1997 (Box 9, Object 81)
      - Various including "Rip Stop" promo and North Sea Jazz Festival, Den Haag, Holland, 1997 (Box 9, Object 82)
      - Various including Very Special Christmas -- Special Olympics concert and 30th NAACP Image Awards, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Object 83)
      - Bob Mills interview; Larry King interview, 1998 Feburary, 1998 April (Box 9, Object 84)
      - United Center, Chicago, Illinois, 1998 April 9 (Box 9, Object 85-87)
      - Spectrum, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1998 April 18 (Box 9, Object 87-89)
      - Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 1998 April 19-1998 April 20 (Box 9, Object 90-91)
      - Earl's Court, London, England with B. B. King and Bonnie Raitt, 1998 October 15-1998 October 17 (Box 9, Object 92-98)
      - Frank Skinner Show, 1999 May 22 (Box 13, Object 135)
      - Crossroads Center guitar auction display, New York, New York, 1999 June 28 (Box 9, Object 99, 101)
      - Madison Square Garden, New York, New York with David Sanborn, Sheryl Crowe, and Bob Dylan, 1999 June 30 (Box 9, Object 100-101)
      - Yokohama Arena, Japan with interview, 1999 November 24 (Box 9, Object 102-104)
      - Various including 41st Grammy Awards with B. B. King and VH-1 Save the Music Concert with Lenny Kravitz and B. B. King, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Object 105)
      - Later with Jools Holland with Bobby Whitlock; Rock and Roll Hall of Fame; 60 Minutes II interview, 2000 (Box 9, Object 106-107)
      - Various including Concert for New York City with Buddy Guy and Queen's Golden Jubilee Party at Buckingham Palace with Paul McCartney, 2000-2002 (Box 9, Object 108)
      - Saratoga, New York, 2001 June 16 (Box 9, Object 109)
      - Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 2001 June 23 (Box 9, Object 110)
      - Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 2001 October 16 (Box 9, Object 111)
      - Buenos Aires, Argentina, 2001 October (Box 9, Object 112)
      - Tokyo, Japan, 2001 December 4 (Box 9, Object 113)
      - Various including Concert for George, Willie Nelson's 70th Birthday Bash, John Mayall's 70th Birthday Concert, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Object 114)
      - Crossroads Guitar Festival, Cotton Bowl, Dallas, Texas, 2004 May (Box 9, Object 115)
      - Sunrise, Florida, 2004 June 15 (Box 9, Object 116)
      - Washington, D.C., 2004 June 21 (Box 9, Object 117)
      - Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 2004 June 29 (Box 9, Object 118)
      - Columbus, Ohio, 2004 July 12 (Box 9, Object 119)
      - Denver, Colorado, 2004 July 21 (Box 9, Object 120-121)
      - Jools Holland's Hootenany, 2004 December 16 (Box 9, Object 122)
      - Jools Holland's Hootenany rehearsals; Tsunami Aid rehearsals; How Can I Help Telethon, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Object 123)
      - Botham on the Fly [U.K. fishing show], 2005 January 7 (Box 9, Object 124-125)
      - Jools Holland Show and rehearsal, 2005 February 13 (Box 9, Object 126)
      - Rock & Roll Years, BBC-4 special, 2005 April 29 (Box 9, Object 127-128)
      - Slowhand at 60 [audio only], 2005 (Box 9, Object 129)
      - Today Show; Cream, Royal Albert Hall DVD trailer, 2005 (Box 9, Object 130)
      - Le Cannet, France, 2006 May 5 (Box 9, Object 131-133)
      - Birmingham, England, 2006 May 11 (Box 9, Object 134)
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 2006 May 23, 2006 May 26 (Box 9, Object 135-136)
      - CBS Sunday Morning, 2006 November 11 (Box 9, Object 137)
      - Osaka, Japan, 2006 November 12, 2006 November 14-2006 November 15 (Box 9, Object 138-140)
      - Tokyo, Japan, 2006 November 23 (Box 9, Object 141)
      - Japanese television with J. J. Cale, 2006 December 8 (Box 9, Object 142)